{
    "subject": "resource/Grey's_Anatomy",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "Gabrielle G. Stanton",
    "human_readable": "The producer of Grey's Anatomy is Gabrielle G. Stanton.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9876486659049988,
            "question": "Is Gabrielle G. Stanton involved in the production of Grey's Anatomy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9851517081260681,
            "question": "What is Gabrielle G. Stanton's role in the production of Grey's Anatomy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.927727460861206,
            "question": "What is Gabrielle G. Stanton known for producing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.805206835269928,
            "question": "Who is the producer of Grey's Anatomy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7939685583114624,
            "question": "Besides Grey's Anatomy, what other shows has Gabrielle G. Stanton been involved with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7805159091949463,
            "question": "What television show did Gabrielle G. Stanton produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7132330536842346,
            "question": "Name a television show produced by Gabrielle G. Stanton."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7005316019058228,
            "question": "What type of television shows does Gabrielle G. Stanton typically produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5378615260124207,
            "question": "Has Gabrielle G. Stanton worked on any popular medical dramas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09315330535173416,
            "question": "Who are some other notable producers of television dramas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The producer of Grey's Anatomy is Gabrielle G. Stanton.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5693_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Gabrielle G. Stanton worked on any popular medical dramas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5693_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of television shows does Gabrielle G. Stanton typically produce?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5693_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a television show produced by Gabrielle G. Stanton.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5693_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5693_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5693_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5693_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5693_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5693_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5693_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5693_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5693_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5693_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5693_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that \"ABC\u2019s drama, Grey\u2019s Anatomy is produced by Gabrielle G. Stanton, Harry Werksman, Mimi Schmir, Peter Nowalk, and Zoanne Clack.\"  This confirms that Gabrielle G. Stanton is a producer of Grey's Anatomy."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as Gabrielle G. Stanton is mentioned multiple times as a producer and writer on Grey's Anatomy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Gabrielle G. Stanton is a producer and has produced the series Grey's Anatomy, among other shows. This supports the statement that Gabrielle G. Stanton is the producer of Grey's Anatomy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}